https://holytrinity.to/privacy-of-personal-information/

Privacy of personal information
Privacy of personal information
These are the privacy practices of Holy Trinity, Toronto.
Mission statement: The Church of the Holy Trinity is a community of people who express Christian faith through lives of integrity, justice and compassion. We foster lay leadership, include the doubter and marginalized, and challenge oppression wherever it may be found.
You can find out more about our history and how we choose to act in the world at our web site at https://holytrinity.to/
Privacy Policy
We are responsible for the personal information we collect or use. Our Privacy Officer is responsible for implementing policies and procedures to protect personal information.
Your personal information is kept in confidence. Your personal information includes your name, address, contact information or any other identifying information about you. Our staff and volunteers are authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained. We have policy safeguards and standard controls to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered.
We collect, use and disclose personal information only for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in light of the circumstances. You may further restrict our use of your data to particular pieces of our work at any time you wish. We commit to complying with PIPEDA and any other privacy laws, codes or regulations which apply to us.
We collect personal information for only the following purposes:
Providing Services
We are not a social service agency and generally do not collect the data of those we directly serve, whether visitors, or people seeking help. However, we may collect information from time to time for one of the following purposes:
to help us meet your request for assistance, we may need information to allow us to communicate on your behalf.To allow us to follow up with you later.
Members, Volunteers, Donors, Event Participants
We collect personal information for the following purposes:
To process and record donations for accounting and tax purposesTo issue charitable tax receipts, if appropriateTo thank contributors for their financial supportTo organize and promote events and other initiativesTo establish and maintain our donor and mailing listsTo respond to a request made by a lawful authority for purposes otherwise required by law
Sharing News, Ideas and Events
We think we have an interesting and engaged community and would like to share what we are doing, what events are coming up, and opportunities to support our ongoing work with your time and other resources.
Personal Information Agreement
We collect, use or disclose your personal information only with your permission. Your permission may be expressed to us in writing or be implied. You may also give us your permission verbally or electronically.
Unless you advise us otherwise, by receiving or reading this Privacy Policy and providing your information, you are deemed to have given us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish us to collect, use or disclose your personal information in the manner set out in this Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer.
You may withdraw your permission to collect, use, store and disclose your personal information at any time, subject to legal and contractual restrictions and reasonable notice.
For further information regarding our privacy policy and practices, please contact our Privacy Officer, Margot Linken at 416-598-4521 x222 or via email to privacy@holytrinity.to
Share this:TwitterFacebookLike this:Like Loading...
WEEKLY GATHERINGS
Sun Worship - 10:30 am (Zoom link)
Wed Coffee Hour - 2:30pm (Zoom link)
Thu Lifting Spirits - 7:15pm (Zoom link)UPCOMING EVENTSCurrent Month
13dec10:30 am12:00 pmVirtual EventSunday Morning worshipthe community gathers together to celebrate and reflect - leadership is shared
Event Details
Sun. 10:30 a.m.Zoom Gatheringin person services cancelled until Sep 1
Our worship is active and shared. We are constantly looking for and
Event Details
Sun. 10:30 a.m.Zoom Gatheringin person services cancelled until Sep 1
Our worship is active and shared. We are constantly looking for and writing liturgy that reflects who we are as a community.
Some of the prayers and hymns we use and that we or our members hold rights to are visible in our Hymns, Psalms and Prayers section. Our recent services have been saved in part and should tell you something about how we worship.
more
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time
(Sunday) 10:30 am - 12:00 pm EDT
LocationHT Zoom Account
CalendarGoogleCal
14dec7:00 pm8:15 pmVirtual EventSpirited Conversations: Martin Luther King - Strength to Loveseeking a spirituality without dogma
Event Details
Register Now
Spirited Conversations continues this month with a
Event Details
Register Now
Spirited Conversations continues this month with a sermon by Martin Luther King suggested by Len Desroches.
The group is friendly and open to new people. The membership is not fixed and changes with the seasons and the material. We meet online about once a month. At each gathering we will focus our discussion around a selected article, podcast or book.
The reading will be emailed to you when you register.
Participants share in the selection of future readings and topics.
Dianne Mesh is an experienced and sensitive facilitator of group discussions of spirituality and faith. She is currently the interim priest on staff at Holy Trinity.Keith Nunn is interested in people and community. He is biblically and theologically literate, but is no longer a  theist. He has been a member of Holy Trinity for more than 25 years.
Some people believe much that the church has traditionally taught. Some believe little but have found ways to stay. Some have left or have thought about it. Some, believing little or none of the dogma of the church are struggling to stay. People holding all these positions are welcome to join the conversation.
more
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time
(Monday) 7:00 pm - 8:15 pm
LocationHoly Trinity19 Trinity Square
Organizer
Dianne and KeithDianne Mesh is an experienced and sensitive facilitator of group discussions of spirituality and faith. She is currently the interim priest on staff at Holy Trinity.
Keith Nunn is interested in people and community. He is biblically and theologically literate, but is no longer a theist. He has been a member of Holy Trinity for more than 25 years.dmesh@holytrinity.to
Holy Trinity19 Trinity Square
CalendarGoogleCal
Related Events
Finding god outside church walls (in person)
16dec12:00 am1:00 amMoved OnlineVirtual EventCoffee Hour
Event Details
We have a kind of cafe gathering every Wednesday from 2:30-3:30pm. Someone will be the host and be online that whole time and folks can drop in and
Event Details
We have a kind of cafe gathering every Wednesday from 2:30-3:30pm. Someone will be the host and be online that whole time and folks can drop in and visit at any point during that time. It’s also a good way to test your Zoom setup. Click here to join the meeting or download the Zoom app.
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time(Wednesday) 12:00 am - 1:00 am
CalendarGoogleCal
20dec10:30 am12:00 pmVirtual EventSunday Morning worshipthe community gathers together to celebrate and reflect - leadership is shared
Event Details
Sun. 10:30 a.m.Zoom Gatheringin person services cancelled until Sep 1
Our worship is active and shared. We are constantly looking for and
Event Details
Sun. 10:30 a.m.Zoom Gatheringin person services cancelled until Sep 1
Our worship is active and shared. We are constantly looking for and writing liturgy that reflects who we are as a community.
Some of the prayers and hymns we use and that we or our members hold rights to are visible in our Hymns, Psalms and Prayers section. Our recent services have been saved in part and should tell you something about how we worship.
more
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time
(Sunday) 10:30 am - 12:00 pm EDT
LocationHT Zoom Account
CalendarGoogleCal
23dec12:00 am1:00 amMoved OnlineVirtual EventCoffee Hour
Event Details
We have a kind of cafe gathering every Wednesday from 2:30-3:30pm. Someone will be the host and be online that whole time and folks can drop in and
Event Details
We have a kind of cafe gathering every Wednesday from 2:30-3:30pm. Someone will be the host and be online that whole time and folks can drop in and visit at any point during that time. It’s also a good way to test your Zoom setup. Click here to join the meeting or download the Zoom app.
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time(Wednesday) 12:00 am - 1:00 am
CalendarGoogleCal
24dec7:15 pm8:45 pmMoved OnlineVirtual EventLifting Spiritsmusic, poetry and cocktails with your host, Keith Nunn
Event Details
music, poetry and cocktails with your host, Keith Nunn
Cocktail hour is a state of mind. It is a little bit of
Event Details
music, poetry and cocktails with your host, Keith Nunn
Cocktail hour is a state of mind. It is a little bit of ritual that helps unwind from a difficult day or can make us more ready to be with others. Booze is optional, but the time that is taken to make oneself a beautiful drink should be celebrated and cherished.
My vision in creating Lifting Spirits is to capture some of the good parts of church (and bar) culture and to bring it into a welcoming and non-dogmatic space where we celebrate art and beauty, take care of each other, listen, celebrate, mourn, and hold. Currently connected to Holy Trinity TO, this is not a religion, it is a way of being with each other with few rules: be kind, listen, seek joy.
Lifting Spirits on YouTube
We start with a little cocktail building session at 7:15pm for about 15 minutes. I’ll post the materials list a few days beforehand in my email broadcast. There is also a Lifting Spirits Channel on YouTube where cocktail information and some performances are collected for your later enjoyment.
Once we have equipped ourselves with a libation, we’ll wander up to my studio for a little open mic, poetry reading and conversation. If you’d like to play something or recite something, that would be fantastic. We can improvise, but it doesn’t hurt if I have some idea how many want to share something beforehand. In between performances we’ll chat. If the numbers grow enough that it’s hard to chat, then we’ll start to use the breakout rooms.
To join my weekly newsletter, click here.
more
Virtual Event Details
Event access information coming soon, Please check back again closer to event start time!
Time
(Thursday) 7:15 pm - 8:45 pm EDT
LocationKeith's Garden Cocktail Lounge
Keith's Garden Cocktail Lounge
CalendarGoogleCal
OFFICE HOURS
9am-5pm, M-F
CHURCH OPEN DOORS
We are mostly closed and operating online, check our calendar for details. A small staff and volunteer team is still distributing sandwiches and some emergency camping gear from 11am-1pm weekdays. To contribute to this, donate online.CONTACT
10 Trinity Sq,
Toronto, ON,
M5G 1B1
416-598-4521
email . twitter . facebook
newsletter . map .
privacy HT Video ChannelComfort, O Comfort! a sermon for Advent 2, Dec 6, 2020 December 6, 2020Advent Two - Holy Trinity TO Sunday Morning Gathering, Dec 6, 2020 December 6, 2020I am Walking
lyrics December 4, 2020O Come O Come
lyrics 3+4 December 4, 2020
X
%d bloggers like this:
